[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "கீறல்",
    "answers": ["கீறல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "கைவினை",
    "answers": ["கைவினை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "சிலேடை",
    "answers": ["சிலேடை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "நுழைவு",
    "answers": ["நுழைவு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "உடமை",
    "answers": ["உடமை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "திறமை",
    "answers": ["திறமை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "தாமிரம்",
    "answers": ["தாமிரம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "ஓரளவு",
    "answers": ["ஓரளவு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "இணக்கம்",
    "answers": ["இணக்கம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "உறைவிடம்",
    "answers": ["உறைவிடம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "தேய்மானம்",
    "answers": ["தேய்மானம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "நுணுக்கம்",
    "answers": ["நுணுக்கம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "துல்லியம்",
    "answers": ["துல்லியம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "ஆணழகன்",
    "answers": ["ஆணழகன்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "ஆபரணம்",
    "answers": ["ஆபரணம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "கொந்தளி",
    "answers": ["கொந்தளி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "கதவு",
    "answers": ["கதவு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "நாள்காட்டி",
    "answers": ["நாள்காட்டி", "எண்", "பண்ணீரெண்டு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "அம்மா",
    "answers": ["அம்மா", "பெண்", "சட்டை", "மேல்சட்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "மருத்துவர்",
    "answers": ["மருத்துவர்", "ஆடவர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "குழந்தை",
    "answers": ["குழந்தை", "சிறுமி", "பாப்பா"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "சான்றிதழ்",
    "answers": ["சான்றிதழ்", "சட்டம்", "தாள்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "கால்",
    "answers": ["கால்", "கால்சட்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "பணப்பை",
    "answers": ["பணப்பை", "கைபேசி", "கைத்தொலைபேசி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "வயதானவர்",
    "answers": ["வயதானவர்", "முதியவர்", "நெற்றி", "வழுக்கை", "தலை", "சொட்டை", "மொட்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "ஆடவர்",
    "answers": ["ஆடவர்", "நோயாளி", "முதுகு", "சட்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "கா வெ டை க் ண் ய்",
    "answers": ["வெண்டைக்காய்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "ம் து ள ப மா ம் ழ",
    "answers": ["மாதுளம்பழம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "மை ச் அ ர் ச",
    "answers": ["அமைச்சர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "ம் ச ன சா",
    "answers": ["சாசனம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "ட ம் ஆ வு ய் க் கூ",
    "answers": ["ஆய்வுக்கூடம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "ய வ தா ர வி ல்ூ",
    "answers": ["தாவரவியல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
